Every single place around the world,
there are dinner tables with families, and
they're arguing and they're talking about
shit, and someone's fucking auntie is
going to say,
"Diet Coke gives you cancer."
And it's at this point that you
can arm your crowd with the knowledge they
need to become a dinner table fucking
genius. And you go,
[clears throat] "Let me cook.
Excuse me, Sandra, I believe
that you just said
that Diet Coke gives you cancer.
You're probably talking about aspartame,
which is broken down into phenylalanine,
aspartic acid, and methanol.
And did you..." And you just fucking tell
that bitch.
And then she sits back and you go, "Look,
you don't know that I watched a reel
earlier on today
that explained all of this
and told me that you should only be
worried about that
if you're a fucking rat. Are you a rat,
Sandra? No.
Well,
shut the fuck up then." So whatever
concepts or area it's...
God, we hate Sandra. Do you feel that?
Whatever area you're in, there
are going to be little pockets of
information that
you can give people so that
when someone at the dinner table says
something, "Oh,
yeah.
Don't want to get too bulky." You're like,
[chuckles] "Let me
cook." Your job with social media,
a lot of the time,
is to create little dinner
table geniuses.
If you can take a complex topic
and make it understandable in 90
seconds, that person,
once they dominate Sandra at the table,
is going to
go, "Fuck, that account online
is incredible." And they're going to
credit
you with how it made them feel.